bajajallianz.com 2014-05-30

# Bajaj Allianz

Privacy Policy  
---  
   
**How does Bajaj Allianz treat data collected from your visit on their sites?**  
   
Our core businesses include protection (property and casualty), private provision (life and health insurance) and portfolio management (asset management). These are confidential matters and Bajaj Allianz and its affiliates recognize your expectations regarding privacy. Bajaj Allianz is committed to keeping your information confidential and secure and that is why we have designed procedures to ensure your privacy in all facets of our relationship. No matter if you are a consumer, a customer, a job applicant or a shareholder, you are protected, not only by the applicable privacy laws, but, more importantly, Bajaj Allianz's commitment to safeguard your privacy and your right to decide how your personal information will be used.  
   
**Notice**  
You can surf all public Bajaj Allianz web-sites anonymously. If we want to collect, process and use personal data from your visit on these sites we will disclose this to you. When you complete an application form, be aware that you are giving personal information and you will not be informed separately. If you decide not to complete the application form or to leave the site altogether, we will not keep any data you have provided.  
\-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------  
   
**Choice**  
If we want to collect information about you, you decide which personal data we receive and how we use it. We will only collect personal data for the purposes you approve of and only to the extent necessary for that purpose. 

In some cases, we may share your data with third parties and affiliates in order to offer you other services. In such cases we respect your right to opt out of such transfer to third parties or affiliates or out of our use of your non-public personal data for purposes other than they were collected for. 

If sensitive data (i.e. about health conditions, racial or ethnic origin, political opinion, religious or philosophical beliefs etc.) is collected on our web-sites at all, we will not transfer them to third parties or affiliates unless you give your express consent.  

\-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------  
   
**Access**  
We respect your privacy rights, particularly your right to access your information. If you ask us, and to the extent provided by Indian law, we will share with you the personal information we collect and retain about you through our web-sites. We strive to keep your data accurate. Please provide us with any changes or corrections in your information.   
**Our employees have to comply with their obligations of secrecy.**  
**Data Security**  
**Bajaj Allianz strives to keep the level of security state-of-the-art at all times.**  
   
**Contact Us**  
|   | Head Office:  
---|---  
  
| Add. | : GE Plaza 1 st Floor, Airport Road, Yerawada,Pune 411006   
---|---  
Tel | : +91-020-66026666  
Fax | : +91-020-66026667  
Email | : [info@bajajallianz.co.in](mailto:info@bajajallianz.co.in)
